Mitch Raznick

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROJECTS

KlipFit for Levi's Denim De-Coded Hackathon - Images

OCT 2022

Worked on a team with Paris-based AI company KlipFit to help Levi's build an interactive size guide that uses body measurements through smartphone cameras. I worked on front-end logic with React and CSS styles/user flows from UX/UI designers.

JULY 2022

Full-stack group project with content sourced from the Art Institute of Chicago's public API. I built front-end logic using React, which included user authentication and API calls to generate content.

Twitter Clone — <u>Deployed</u> | <u>Github</u> (Back End)

AUG 2022

My General Assembly cohort worked as a team to recreate Twitter. My role was with the back end team, building views, serializers, paths, and endpoints using Python and Django.

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, New York, NY - Software Engineering Fellow

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

Completed over 480 hours of coding, and built around 35 web apps, programs, and sites over the course of 13 weeks as part of the Software Engineering Immersive program.

ButterflyMX, New York, NY - Sales Director

JAN 2022 - MAY 2022

Prospected 50+ multi-family real estate leads per day; Managed a Salesforce and Hubspot pipelines; Built and presented a sales deck and software demo of our smart intercoms 3-6 times per day to developers, owners, property managers, and more; Generated over \$10K ARR in my first quarter.

Angi Leads, New York, NY — *Inside Sales Manager*

JULY 2018 - DEC 2021

Developed and managed a team of 10-14 reps for B2B sales; Used datamining software to generate thousands of leads per week; Selected to lead company workshops for various best practices; Awarded top sales team in December 2018; Analyzed weekly sales data to successfully improve metrics and performance, and achieved highest-revenue manager in Q3 2021 following a re-brand from HomeAdvisor and verticalization.

Angi Leads, New York, NY — Senior Online Marketing Consultant

JUNE 2016 - JULY 2018

Made over 250 lifetime B2B sales by using best practices in CRM pipeline management, pitching strategies, and outreach methods; Served as team lead and secondary coach alongside team manager; Built member profiles using SEO terms to boost consumer interaction; Four-time MVP winner in director group.

CONTACT & LINKS

mraznick@gmail.com
Portfolio
Github
402-980-4919
Brooklyn, NY

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

HTML CSS

JavaScript React/React Native

Python Node.js

Mongoose MongoDB

Express Axios

Django Flask

SQL Postgres

Netlify Heroku

Wordpress Wix

SUMMARY

I'm a creative, problem-solving, impact-driven developer with an eye for design. I'm able to leverage my 6 years in tech sales to exhibit great skills in communication, delivery, and teamwork. My career change from tech sales to software engineering is fueled by my creative foundation and educational background, my passion to build, and the analytical mindset gained from tech sales. I can bring efficiency and poise to fast-paced environments to achieve team goals with tight deadlines.

EDUCATION

General Assembly NYC Software Engineering Immersive MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

The University of Kansas
William Allen White School of Journalism
BS in Journalism: News & Information
Minor in Film & Media Studies
AUG 2011 - AUG 2015